aoi hoshi ni senritsu ga hashiru
a
o
i
ho
shi
ni
se
n
ri
tsu
ga
ha
shi
ru
A shudder runs over the blue planet
푸른 지구에 전율이 흐른다
kuroi arashi chikazuku toki
ku
ro
i
a
ra
shi
chi
ka
zu
ku
to
ki
It's the time the dark storm approaches
검은 폭풍이 닥쳐오는 순간
kokoro no oku de mezameru HERO
ko
ro
no
o
ku
de
me
za
ru
HE
RO
It's as if a hero is awakening on the inside
마음 속의 눈을 뜬 영웅들이여
tobitatsu no da furimukazu ni
to
bi
ta
tsu
no
da
fu
ri
mu
ka
zu
ni
Fly away and don't look back!
뒤돌아보지 말고 날아가라
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Brave Command Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
DAGWON kagayake DAGWON
DA
G
WON
ka
ga
ya
ke
DA
G
WON
Dagwon... Shine on!! Dagwon!
다그온 빛나라!! 다그온
heiwa mamoru namae sa
he
i
wa
ma
mo
ru
na
ma
e
sa
The name that protects the peace
평화를 지키는 이름이다
DAGWON oretachi DAGWON
DA
G
WON
o
re
ta
chi
DA
G
WON
Dagwon! We are Dagwon!
다그온 우리는 다그온
yume wa zettai watasanai
yu
me
wa
ze
t
ta
i
wa
ta
sa
na
i
We will never hand over our dream
꿈은 절대로 넘겨줄 수 없다
afureru yuuki te ni shitai nara
a
fu
re
ru
yu
u
ki
te
ni
shi
ta
i
na
ra
To grab the overflowing courage
넘쳐흐르는 용기를 거머쥐고 싶다면
tsuyoku tsuyoku yuujou shinjiru koto sa
tsu
yo
ku
tsu
yo
ku
yu
u
jo
shi
n
ji
ru
ko
to
sa
We believe in our friendship firmly
우리 우정을 굳게 믿는 거다
kizutsuku koto mo osore wa shinai
ki
zu
tsu
ku
ko
to
mo
o
so
re
wa
shi
na
i
We are not afraid of getting hurt
상처입는 것도 두렵지 않아
mugendai no mirai wo egaku sono tame ni
mu
ge
n
da
i
no
mi
ra
i
wo
e
ga
ku
so
no
ta
me
ni
In order to reach that infinite future!
무한대의 미래를 그려내기 위해서라면
I'm so hungry.
아아~ 배고프다
Hey, what're ya having, Kai?
어? 뭐야, 카이?
Set meal again?
또 정식이냐?
Unnecessary assistance.
쓸데없는 참견 마라
You're still not disgusted after eating same thing?
매일 똑같은걸 먹고도 용케 안 질리는구만
Hey, that!
저거... 저거!
Sankai High School news.
산카이 고등학교 뉴스
Today's scoop!
오늘의 특종!
We will find out the secret of Shin Sawamura, the Judo club captain!
유도부 주장, 사와부라 신 군의 비밀을 밝힌다!
It seems that I became famous!
나도 유명해 졌다는 거구만
-Secret?
-Could it be about Dagwon?!
-비밀?
-설마 다그온의!?
Rampage! Dag Armor
폭주 다그 아머
Space Witch Succubus
Appears
우주 마녀 서큐버스 등장
When we went to the club room, the members were in the midst of training.
부실을 방문했을 때, 유도부원은 한참 대련중이었습니다
But we can't find Shin Sawamura here.
하지만, 사와무라 신의 모습은 보이지 않는군요
Meanwhile, Sawamura was wandering around in the school.
그시각, 사와무라 군은 교내를 배회하고 있었습니다
And we witnessed something even we can't believe!
그리고, 우리들은 믿겨지지 않는 장면을 목격했습니다!
What the? He was asking for a date to all girls one after another!
보십시오, 그는 끊임없이 닥치는대로 여학생에게 데이트 신청을 하고 있었습니다!
But the result was miserable.
하지만, 그 결과는 비참했습니다
When will he ever be able to pick up a girl?!
과연 그가 데이트에 성공하는 날은 언제인가!?
On next time, we'll find out the secret of Maria Tobe, the head of Supernatural Phenomenon Research Club!
다음회에는 초상현상(超常現象) 연구회의 부장 토베 마리아 씨의 비밀을 밝히겠습니다
Please look forward!
기대하세요!
-It was a big success!
-It really was nothing.
-대성공이야
-별거 아니잖아
But it was difficult to take pictures in secret!
하지만, 몰래카메라 찍는거 힘들었어
I'm sorry...
죄송합니다...
Alright. I'll forgive.
알았다, 용서하지
-Instead.
-Instead...?
-그 대신
-그 대신?
Let's have a date!
데이트 하자~
Date?
데이트...?
-Isn't it a good idea?
-It's not...
-어때, 좋잖아?
-고, 곤란합니다
What was that-
무, 무슨 짓거...
Erika senpai!
에리카 선배!
How low are you, to enter someone else's club room and surprise underclassmen?
당신, 남의 부실에 맘대로 들어와서 하급생을 놀래키다니, 저질이야!
Get out right now!
어서 나가줘!
Erika...
에리카 쨩...
Heya, celebrity!
여어! 유명인
Erika...
에리카 쨩...
Next! Yamada!
다음, 야마다!
Start!
시작!
Stop! Match set!
한판! 거기까지!
What happened to our captain?
어떻게 된거냐, 주장?
Did he catch cold?
감기라도 걸린 거 아냐?
Erika...
에리카 쨩...
Next! Sakada!
자, 다음! 사카다!
We got a result.
나왔어
The world.
「The World」 : 달성
The best affection. A best couple is born.
최고의 애정, 베스트 커플 탄생
The lovers.
「The Lovers」 : 결합
Love at first sight. A crush will bear fruit.
첫눈에 반함, 짝사랑이 결실을 맺는다
Love fortunetelling?
사랑점(戀占い)?
Don't worry about things. Just make up a mind and confess, and then you will be Lucky.
이래저래 고민하지 말고, 결심해서 고백하면 Lucky
Alright! I'll do it! I will!
좋아! 난 하겠어! 해 보겠어!
Wait for me, Erika!
기다려줘! 에리카 쨩!
I... I met Dagwon here for the first time.
나... 아아, 저는 이곳에서 처음으로 다그온과...
I was looking for you, Erika!
찾아다녔어, 에리카 쨩!
Sawamura! What was that for?
사와무라 군! 뭐하는 거야?
What do you want this time? Revenge for a moment ago?
이번엔 뭐지? 아까의 복수를 하러 온 거야?
N- no way!
마, 말도 안돼
I heard that you were making a documentary about Dagwons!
다그온의 다큐멘터리를 찍는다고 들었는데...
It has nothing to do with you.
당신과는 상관 없잖아
Then you could have told me at the beginning!
그렇다면, 처음부터 나한테 말해줬으면 좋았을텐데 말야
Actually, I am a friend of Dagwon.
사실, 난 다그온과는 아는 사이야
Really?
정말?
That liar.
거짓말쟁이
But before that, I have something important to tell you.
하지만, 그전에 중요한 할 말이 있어
Erika, be- become...
에리카 쨩, 나, 나의...
Become my girlfriend!
내 애인이 되어줘!
What persistent jerk you are.
참 질리지도 않는구나
-Are you trying to seduce me this time?
-N- no way!
-이번엔 나한테 수작 거는거야?
-아, 아니야
I know it's a lie that you're a friend of Dagwon!
다그온과 아는 사이라고 거짓말이나 치고 말야
I- I'm not lying!
저, 정말이야!
Everyone, let's move.
얘들아, 다른데로 가자
W- wait for me!
기, 기다려줘!
Please wait!
기다려줘!
-Erika!
-Unhand me.
-에리카 쨩!
-이거 놔!
Please, listen to me...
부탁이야, 내 이야기를...
No!
싫어!
You stalker!
이 스토커!
What was that for?!
이게 뭐하는 짓이야!
I- I'm... sorry...
저기... 미안해
From now on, do not approach me closer than 10 meters.
이제부터 내 반경 10m 이내에는 접근하지 말아줘
That idiot! He actually believed in Maria's fortunetelling!
바보녀석, 마리아의 점 같은걸 진짜 믿다니 말야
Wait for me!
기다려~
Sawamura?
사와무라 군~♡
I was sorry about that before.
아까는 미안했어
That's for me to say.
나야말로
You are already mine.
이미 당신은 나의 것
Shin Sawamura... no, Dag Armor.
사와무라 신... 아니, 다그 아머
A Dagwon!
다그온이다!
Did an alien appear again?
또, 또 우주인이 나타난 건가?
It's a Dagwon. Did something happen?
다그온입니다 뭔가 사건이라도 일어난 것일까요?
-What's going on?
-I don't know.
-어떻게 된거지?
-모르겠어
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Original Korean Subtitles by Jaebari (재바리)
Translated to English by Subdivers
Checked by Great Exkaiser103
자막 원본(번역): 재바리
수정: Subdivers
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
용자지령
다그온
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온!!
Turbo Kai!
터보 카이!!
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온!!
Wing Yoku!
윙 요쿠!!
Try Dagwon!
트라이 다그온!!
Fire En!
파이어 엔!!
-What are you thinking, Dag Armor?!
-Why are you doing this?!
-뭘 어쩔 셈이냐, 다그 아머!
-어째서 이런 짓을!?
He was jilted by someone he liked.
좋아하던 애한테 퇴짜맞았어
To vent that anger...
그 분풀이로...
Merging Fusion!
융합합체(融合合體)!!
Dag Fire!
다그 파이어!!
Hey, hey, hey, you!
야 야 야 야 야, 너!
There's no use venting it on us!
우리한테 화풀이를 해도 소용 없잖아!
You jerk!
이자식!
-Is he really trying to vent it out?
-No, he should be already got used to being jilted.
-설마, 정말로 화풀이를 하려고...
-아니, 녀석은 퇴짜맞는 것에 익숙해져 있어
That's nothing to him.
새삼스레 그런 것에...
Could he be controlled...?
설마, 조종당하고 있는 건...?
By an alien from Sargasso?
사르갓소의 우주인?
Seems so.
아마 그런 것 같아
-Alright. Let's split and find.
-Got it.
-좋아, 흩어져서 찾아보자
-네
That's enough!
작작 좀 해라!
Damn! It's nonsensical to destroy the village to vent it out!
제길! 분풀이로 마을을 부수다니, 말도 안돼!
What are you doing here?
이런 곳에서 뭘!?
Wh- what?!
아, 아니!?
I'll make you comfortable.
지금 편하게 해주마
You bastard!
이자식!
Dag Armor is my...
다그 아머는 나의,
Space Witch Succubus' puppet.
우주 마녀 서큐버스 님의 꼭두각시
Kill each others, Dagwon!
다그온끼리 서로 죽여라!
She knows the true identity of us!
녀석은 우리들의 정체를 알고 있어!
She disguised as Ms. Erika and approached to Shin! What cowardice!
에리카 씨로 변해서 신에게 접근한 거군요! 비겁한 녀석!
But we still have something.
하지만, 이쪽에도 방법이 있다
Ryu, respond!
류, 응답해라!
He came!
왔습니다!
Uh, what do you want?
저기, 대체...
We have something to ask.
너에게 부탁이 있어
Please persuade Dag Armor.
다그 아머를 설득해 줘
Why me?
어째서 제가?
Dag Armor is weak to pretty girls.
다그 아머는 미소녀에게 약해
Pretty girl?
미소녀?
But how?
하지만, 어떻게?
Use that.
저걸 쓴다
Stop it, Dag Armor!
그만둬, 다그 아머!
Please... please!
부탁이야, 부탁이야!
Wake up!
정신 차려!
Aren't you the brave hero of justice?
당신은 정의의 용자잖아?
Please stop fighting against your comrades!
동료끼리 싸우는건 그만둬
Listen to me, Dag Armor!
내 말을 들어줘, 다그 아머!
You must not listen to such brat.
저런 녀석의 말에 귀를 귀울여선 안돼
-Are you alright?
-Y- yes...
-상처는 없나?
-네, 네...
We'll have to perform Merging Fusion!
할 수 없어, 융합합체다!!
Me?
나...?
Now, Dag Armor, show your loyalty to me!
자, 다그 아머!
나에 대한 충성을 보여라!
R- run away!
도, 도망쳐!
Dag Armor!
다그 아머!
Hurry up!
서둘러!
Stop that!
그만둬!
No!
싫어!
Let me go!
이거 놔!
No!
싫어!
Kill her!
해치워 버려!
Unhand me! Let me go!
이거 놔! 놓으라구!
Stop! Please stop!
그만둬, 이제 그만둬!
Stop that...
그, 그만둬!
Unhand me! Unhand me, you stalker!
이거 놔! 놓으라니까! 이 스토커!
That hurts!
아퍼~!
Erika...
에... 리... 카...
Dag Armor...
다그 아머...
Wh- what are you doing?!
뭐, 뭘 하는 거야!?
Dag Armor!
다그 아머!
N- no way!
마, 말도 안돼!
How... how dare you fool me!
잘도... 잘도 날 바보취급 했겠다!
Alright, I'll face you.
좋아, 상대해 주마
How do I look? I'm pretty, ain't I?
어떠냐, 아름답지?
To hell with your look!
큭, 밥 맛 떨어진다!!
You are my puppet.
넌 내 꼭두각시란 말이다
Wh- who would ever become your...
누, 누가 너 따위의...
Dag Armor!
다그 아머!
Don't give up, Dag Armor!
힘내! 다그 아머!!
Erika?!
에리카!?
Graviton Kick!
그라비톤 킥!!
I'm not losing you!
놓치지... 않는다!!
Final Buster!
파이널 버스터!!
Erika!
에~리카 쨩!
Thank you, about yesterday. I was saved thanks to you.
어제는 고마웠어
덕분에 살았다구
Hey, you.
저기 말야
If you keep being persistent, I'll call my boyfriend to teach you a lesson!
계속 끈질기게 굴면 남자친구 불러서 혼내달라 그런다!
My boyfriend is scary when he's angry!
내 남자친구, 화나면 무섭다구
Wh- who?!
누, 누구!?
He is Dag Armor.
그 사람, 다그 아머니까 말야
See you.
그럼, 안녕~
Dag Armor... that would mean...
다그 아머... 라는건?!
E- Erika!
에, 에리카 쨩!
Also, didn't I tell you not to approach me closer than 10 meters?
그리고, 반경 10m 이내에 접근하지 말라고 말했잖아
You...
이...
Actually, I am Dag-
사실은 내가 다그...
...stalker!
스토커!
No way!
이럴수가~!?
The sun suddenly called me
태양이 갑작스레 나를 불러내서
taiyou ga fui ni ore wo izanau
To come to the blue sea
푸르게 비치는 바다로 만나러 갔지
aoku sukitooru umi ni ai ni kita
The ripples are coming and going
밀려왔다 돌아가는 잔물결
yosete wa kaesu sazanami
An endless melody
멈추지 않는 멜로디
tomaru koto nai MELODY
sono sugata towa ni tsunagu you ni
To keep that shape for eternity
그 모습을 영원히 유지할 수 있도록
I'll follow the fate of the dream
꿈의 행방을 뒤쫓아 갈 거야
oikakete yuku yo yume no yukue
Sparkling far away
멀리서 반짝이던
tooku kirameita
kaze no naka no PRISM
A Prism in the Wind
바람 속의 프리즘
Yuusha Shirei
Dagwon
Preview for Next Episode
용자지령
다그온
차회예고
A boss in Fuun High School, Geki Kuroiwa.
풍운 고등학교 번장, 쿠로이와 게키
He's my opponent!
내 싸움 상대야
But I have no time to deal with you for now!
하지만, 지금은 네 상대를 하고 있을 수 없어
Zargoss Seijin was waiting for Dagwon when we emergency dispatched.
긴급 출동한 다그온을 기다리고 있던 것은 자고스 성인이었어
The missile they shot has exploded!
녀석들이 발사한 미사일이 대폭발!
In this rate, the Earth will become Zargoss Seijin's planet!
이대론 지구는 자고스 성인의 별이 되어버려!
Next time on Yuusha Shirei Dagwon! Flashing Dag Base
다음회 용자지령 다그온
섬광의 다그 베이스
Our base is about to move!
우리들의 기지가 움직이기 시작한다!
Flashing Dag Base
섬광의 다그 베이스